<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">thINKAR</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="title_activity_download">Download a Marker</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About thINK</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contact">Contact thINK</string>

    <string name="think_logo">thINK Logo</string>

    <!-- Nav Drawer Content -->
    <string name="drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string-array name="nav_array">
        <item>AR Browser</item>
        <item>thINK 2016</item>
        <item>About thINK</item>
        <item>Contact thINK</item>
        <item>Download a Marker</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="drawer_footer">© 2016 thINK</string>

    <!-- ActivityMain Content -->
    <string name="main_body">Explore augmented reality experiences at thINK events and in thINK communications.</string>
    <string name="btn_go">GO</string>

    <!-- ActivityAbout Content -->
    <string name="about_body"><b>thINK</b> is an independent community of Canon Solutions America Production Print customers, solution partners, and print industry experts. Led by some of
        the most successful inkjet service providers in the country, it provides a forum for members to network, gain knowledge, discuss common challenges, and share best practices.\n\nThe
        inaugural event of the community of Canon Solutions America Production Print inkjet customers drew more than 350 attendees, making it the largest user group event for inkjet
        production printing. <b>thINK</b> 2016 promises to be even bigger and better – with expanded conference sessions and projected attendance of more than 400. </string>

    <!-- ActivityContact Content -->
    <string name="contact_title">Contact thINK</string>
    <string name="contact_body">The thINK Executive Director and Board Members welcome your input, questions, and comments. Would you like to share your ideas, opinions, and best practices
        with the community? Do you have suggestions for a blog post, educational session, or community resource that will help you grow your business? Have a question about how you can get
        involved? Please <b>click on this link</b> and fill out the form to send us a message.</string>
    <string name="contact_footer">© 2016 thINK</string>

    <!-- ActivityDownload Content -->
    <string name="download_message">Tap the image to print.</string>

    <!-- ActivityThink Content -->
    <string name="think__table_status">Status</string>
    <string name="think__table_vendor">Vendor</string>
    <string name="think__table_booth">Booth</string>
    <string name="think_circle_label">0/30</string>

    <!-- ActivityThink Content -->
    <string name="rules_title">How to Play the Game</string>
    <string name="rules_subheader">VISIT THE PARTNER PAVILION!</string>
    <string name="rules_body">Each partner has a special postcard waiting for you. All of them have an augmented reality experience inside. Some could make you an <b>instant winner</b>.</string>
    <string name="rules_list_1">1. Collect a greeting at every partner table</string>
    <string name="rules_list_2">2. Watch the AR experience with the thINK AR app to find out if you are an instant winner</string>
    <string name="rules_list_3">3. Visit the TREKK booth to get your last greeting and enter the grand prize drawing</string>
    <string name="rules_list_4">4. Post about it on social media using the hashtag: <b>#GreetingsfromthINK</b></string>
    <string name="rules_disclaimer">*Grand Prize winners (chosen by random drawing) will be announced Wednesday morning.</string>

    <!-- InstantWinner Content -->
    <string name="instant_winner_body">You’re An Instant Winner! Claim your prize at the Canon Solutions America area</string>
    <string name="instant_winner">Instant Winner</string>
    <string name="close">X</string>

</resources>